** Testing getQuestions **
-------------------------------
-> getQuestions():
[ 'Q1', 'Q2', 'Q3' ]

** Testing getAnswers **
-------------------------------
-> getAnswers():
[ 'A1', 'A2', 'A3' ]

** Testing getQuestionsAnswers **
-------------------------------
-> getQuestionsAnswers():
[
  { question: 'Q1', answer: 'A1' },
  { question: 'Q2', answer: 'A2' },
  { question: 'Q3', answer: 'A3' }
]

** Testing getQuestion **
-------------------------------
-> getQuestion():
{
  error: 'Question number must be an integer',
  question: '',
  number: ''
}
-> getQuestion(0):
{ error: 'Question number must be >= 1', question: '', number: '' }
-> getQuestion(1):
{ error: '', question: 'Q1', number: 1 }
-> getQuestion(4):
{
  error: 'Question number must be less than the number of questions (3)',
  question: '',
  number: ''
}

** Testing getAnswer **
-------------------------------
-> getAnswer():
{ error: 'Answer number must be an integer', answer: '', number: '' }
-> getAnswer(0):
{ error: 'Answer number must be >= 1', answer: '', number: '' }
-> getAnswer(1):
{ error: '', answer: 'A1', number: 1 }
-> getAnswer(4):
{
  error: 'Answer number must be less than the number of questions (3)',
  answer: '',
  number: ''
}

** Testing getQuestionAnswer **
-------------------------------
-> getQuestionAnswer():
{
  error: 'Question number must be an integer',
  question: '',
  number: ''
}
-> getQuestionAnswer(0):
{ error: 'Question number must be >= 1', question: '', number: '' }
-> getQuestionAnswer(1):
{ error: '', question: 'Q1', number: 1, answer: 'A1' }
-> getQuestionAnswer(4):
{
  error: 'Question number must be less than the number of questions (3)',
  question: '',
  number: ''
}
{ error: '', question: 'Q1', number: 1, answer: 'A1' } 